&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们了解原型，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We understand prototypes,
我们理解它们上面的句法糖分，这就是类系统。
we understand the syntactic sugar on top of them which is the class system.
但是让我们看看使用这个原型系统的另一种方式，我相信
But let's look at another way of using this prototype system, which I believe
将在JavaScript中发现更多潜在的未来探索。
will uncover more potential future exploration within JavaScript.
我相信我们还可以完成更多的事情，而且
I believe there's more things that we can accomplish, and
我认为我们可以用一种更简单的方式来做。
I think we can do it in a simpler way.
所以我想让我们简化。
So I want us to simplify.
我有一种不同的风格来处理我们使用对象的方式，并且
I have a different style of approaching the way we use objects, and
它们之间的原型语言
the prototype language between them and
我把这种编码风格称为Oloo，即链接到其他对象的对象。
I call this style of coding OLOO, Objects Linked to Other Objects.
我需要一些朗朗上口的术语来与OO和
I needed some kind of catchy term to contrast with OO and
可悲的现实是面向对象实际上是最好的术语。
the sad reality is that object oriented is actually the best term.
如果你仔细想想，面向类的语言
If you think about it, class oriented languages
不应该真的称自己为面向对象的语言。
should never have really called themselves object oriented languages.
他们应该称自己是以班级为导向的。
They should have called themselves class oriented.
但是他们接受了那个面向对象的绰号，现在它被卡住了
But they took on that object oriented moniker, and now it's stuck and
我们不能重新使用面向对象的含义。
we can't re-purpose the meaning of object oriented.
但如果你真的想一想，有两种语言存在，
But if you really think about it there are two languages in existence,
JavaScript是其中之一，Oloo是另一个。
JavaScript being one of them, OLOO being the other.
据我所知有两种语言
Two languages in existence to my knowledge
在中，您可以创建没有任何类的对象。
where in you can create an object without any class.
所以当你真正想一想的时候，唯一两种真正面向对象的语言
So when you really think about it, the only two truly object oriented languages
是Oloo和JavaScript。
are OLOO and JavaScript.
但那艘船已经启航了。
But that ship has sailed.
我们不能使用OO，所以让我们称之为Oloo，即链接到其他对象的对象。
We can't use OO, so let's call it OLOO, Objects Linked to Other Objects.
这是商标，
And that is trademarked,
所以如果你想用的话你需要付给我很多钱。
so you need to pay me lots of money if you want to use it.
我开玩笑的。
I'm kidding.
让我们看看Oloo是如何处理事情的。
So let's look at how OLOO approaches things.
记住类语法。
Remember the class syntax.
这就是我们之前谈到的。
This is what we talked about a little bit before.
类是模式的一种方式
Classes are a way of patterning
不同实体之间的一些关系并实例化它们。
some relationship between different entities and instantiating them.
但在被子底下记住
But under the covers, remember,
那个类实际上暗示了所有这些粘性物质，对吗？
that that class is actually implying all of this gunk right?
它实际上暗示了所有这些原型。
It's actually implying all of these prototypes.
所以如果我们可以做一种风格的编码来完成同样的事情，但是
So what if we could do a style of coding that accomplishes the same thing but
没有任何用类思考或设计的包袱，
without any of the baggage of thinking or designing with classes,
需要担心原型，或超级，或任何其他东西，以及
needing to worry about prototypes, or super, or any of that other stuff, and
当然再也不需要使用新的关键字了。
certainly never needing to use the new key word again.
如果我们可以让对象链接到其他对象会怎么样？
What if we could just make objects link to other objects?
下面是该代码的Oloo风格表示。
Here's the OLOO style representation of that code.
我想让你在这里看到的是，我现在只有物体了。
What I want you to see here is that I have only objects now.
车间不是一个功能。
Workshop is not a function.
这不是一门课。
It's not a class.
这只是一个物体。
It's just an object.
另一个工作坊只是一个对象。
AnotherWorkshop is just an object.
我正在通过对象链接它。创建工作坊，但它只是一个对象。
I am linking it via Object.create the workshop but it is just an object.
而JSRecentParts只是一个链接到另一个工作坊的对象。
And the JSRecentParts is just an object that is linked to another workshop.
因此，当我调用JSRecentPart.setTeacher时，它没有该方法，但它
So when I call JSRecentPart.setteacher, it doesn't have that method but it
去了另一个没有那个方法的研讨会，但是它去了这个研讨会。
goes to another workshop who doesn't have that method, but it goes to this workshop.
然后它找到SET Teacher，并使用调用站点的这个绑定
And then it finds set teacher, and it uses this binding of the call site
若要设置JSRecentPart的属性，请执行以下操作。
to set a property on JSRecentPart's.
所以我们得到了同样的阶级制度的好处。
So we're getting the same benefits of a class system.
但请注意现在缺少了什么。
But notice what is missing now.
我们没有更多的.Prototype，我们没有更多的构造函数，
We don't have any more .prototypes, we don't have any more constructor functions,
而且我们没有更多的新关键词。
and we don't have any more new keywords.
我们只是将对象链接到其他对象，
We just have objects linked to other objects,
这里的魔术是我们用这个小东西叫做
and the magic trick here is that we use this little thing called
创建对象来创建和链接我们的对象。
object.create to make and link our objects.
所以反对。创建，显然不是我发明的。
So object.create, I obviously didn't invent that.
这是在ES5中添加到语言中的。
That was added to the language back in ES5.
这实际上是我们的好朋友Doug Crockford为JavaScript提出的。
That was actually proposed for JavaScript by our good friend Doug Crockford.
他想出了对象的想法。创建和
He came up with the idea for object.create and
他让委员会通过了，并加入了ES5。
he got it pushed through the committee and added to ES5.
好主意道格。
Great idea Doug.
太棒了。
Fantastic.
这是我在JavaScript中最喜欢的功能之一。
This is one of my favorite features in JavaScript.
作为一个有点悲哀的附注，Doug Crockford后来否认了object。create和
As a little sad side note, Doug Crockford has since disowned object.create and
不再认为我们应该使用它，这让我哭了一滴眼泪。
no longer thinks that we should use it at all, which makes me a cry a little tear.
我喜欢这个功能，因为我喜欢能够制作对象和
I love this feature because I love being able to make objects and
将它们链接在一起，而不会有任何关于new的废话，并且
link them together without any of the nonsense of new, and
原型、构造函数、类、扩展以及所有其他东西。
prototypes, and constructors, and classes, and extends, and all of that other stuff.
我喜欢能够充分利用面向对象的优势
I love just being able to take full advantage of the objects oriented
JavaScript中的系统。
system in JavaScript.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不仅认为这是一种更简单的风格，而且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Not only do I argue that this is a simpler style and
如果您逐行比较，基本上很少有语法
if you looked line by line comparison, there is essentially very little syntactic
这个和类的等价物之间的区别。
difference between this and the class equivalent.
这并不是说类的等价物只是大量的含糖或其他东西。
It's not that class equivalent is just massively more sugary or something.
它们在本质上是非常接近的。
They're essentially very close in equivalence.
但是这个直接暴露给你的地方
But where this one is exposing to you directly instead
假装它不是什么东西，
of pretending with an artifice that it's something that it's not,
它直接暴露给你，这些只是链接到其他对象的对象。
it's exposing to you directly, these are just objects linked to other objects.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么，object.create是如何做到这一点的呢？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, how does object.create do that magic?
好的，这是一个旧的对象填充。创建。
Well this is an old polyfill for object.create.
我们不再需要主要用于ES5之前的聚合填充。
We don't need polyfills mostly for pre-ES5 anymore.
但这是针对object.create的ES5之前的polyfill。
But this was the pre-ES5 polyfill for object.create.
看看它做了什么，是不是真的产生了一个空函数。
And look at what it does, is it literally makes an empty function.
因为我们甚至不关心函数是什么。
Cuz we don't even care what the function is.
它将其原型设置为sum O，并调用new on
It sets its prototype to sum O, and it calls new on
关心给我们新创建的对象的任何功能的人。
that who cares whatever function to give us the newly created object.
所以，换句话说，方式object.create就是Oloo的魔力，
So, in other words, the way object.create does the magic of OLOO,
就是我们把所有那些没人关心的构造函数
is we take all of those constructor functions that nobody cares about and
所有那些没人想写的.原型，而且
all those .prototypes that nobody wants to write, and
所有那些新的关键词都是令人困惑的。
all those new keywords that are just confusing.
我们把它们藏在物体里面。创造，好的，
And we hide them inside of object.create, okay,
在我们的代码中只留下对象之间这种干净、简单的链接。
leaving in our code just this clean, simple linkage between objects.